export const data2= [
    {
      question: "If 3x - 7 = 17, then what is the value of 6x - 5?",
      option1: "17",
      option2: "19",
      option3: "24",
      option4: "34",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "A train travels 75% of the distance at a speed of 30 km/hr. What should be the speed of the train to cover the remaining distance in 1 hour?",
      option1: "90 km/hr",
      option2: "100 km/hr",
      option3: "120 km/hr",
      option4: "150 km/hr",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "The sum of ages of 5 children born at the intervals of 3 years each is 50 years. What is the age of the youngest child?",
      option1: "4 years",
      option2: "5 years",
      option3: "6 years",
      option4: "8 years",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "If a quarter kilogram of potato costs 60 cents, how much will 2.5 kilograms of potato cost?",
      option1: "$1.40",
      option2: "$1.50",
      option3: "$1.80",
      option4: "$2.40",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "If A : B = 2 : 3 and B : C = 4 : 5, then what is A : B : C?",
      option1: "4 : 6 : 5",
      option2: "8 : 12 : 15",
      option3: "10 : 15 : 12",
      option4: "12 : 15 : 20",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "In a class of 60 students, 30% are girls. How many boys are there in the class?",
      option1: "24",
      option2: "30",
      option3: "36",
      option4: "42",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "The length of a rectangle is twice its breadth. If the perimeter of the rectangle is 72 cm, then what is the length of the rectangle?",
      option1: "18 cm",
      option2: "24 cm",
      option3: "30 cm",
      option4: "36 cm",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "If 8x - 3y = 12 and 2x + 5y = 4, then what is the value of 3x - 2y?",
      option1: "0",
      option2: "1",
      option3: "2",
      option4: "3",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "If the selling price of an item is twice the cost price, then what is the profit percentage?",
      option1: "50%",
      option2: "75%",
      option3: "100%",
      option4: "150%",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the missing number in the sequence: 3, 6, 12, ?, 48, 96",
      option1: "18",
      option2: "24",
      option3: "30",
      option4: "36",
      ans: 2,
    }
  ];
  